{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02a738d248d1874fedb08"),
	"Ans" : "\"1\"",
	"Option1" : "Orange Juice",
	"Option2" : "Ravi",
	"Option3" : "Richard Parker",
	"Option4" : "Pi",
	"Question" : "Who has the worst sickness?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0001",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02ad88d248d1874fedb09"),
	"Ans" : "\"1\"",
	"Option1" : "Pondicherry",
	"Option2" : "Toronto",
	"Option3" : "Munnar",
	"Option4" : "Zurich",
	"Question" : "Where does Pi grow up?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0002",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02b5e8d248d1874fedb0a"),
	"Ans" : "\"3\"",
	"Option1" : "He resembles a famous actor named Richard Parker",
	"Option2" : "Pi names him after favourite teacher",
	"Option3" : "A clerical error",
	"Option4" : "His zookeeper names him after himself",
	"Question" : "How does Richard Parker get his name?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0003",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02caa8d248d1874fedb0c"),
	"Ans" : "\"4\"",
	"Option1" : "That the raft is undamaged",
	"Option2" : "That Richard Parker was subdued by the storm",
	"Option3" : "That the food stores survived",
	"Option4" : "That one whistle is not lost, so he can still control Richard Parker",
	"Question" : "What does Pi consider to be his saving grace after the big storm?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0005",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02d008d248d1874fedb0d"),
	"Ans" : "\"2\"",
	"Option1" : "Buddhism",
	"Option2" : "Hinduism",
	"Option3" : "Islam",
	"Option4" : "Christianity",
	"Question" : "What is Pi's first religion?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0006",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02d508d248d1874fedb0e"),
	"Ans" : "\"4\"",
	"Option1" : "His Religion",
	"Option2" : "His Family",
	"Option3" : "His Past",
	"Option4" : "Time",
	"Question" : "What did Pi forget that made his ordeal easier?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0007",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02db58d248d1874fedb0f"),
	"Ans" : "\"2\"",
	"Option1" : "Bits of chocolate",
	"Option2" : "His Leather Shoe",
	"Option3" : "Biscuits",
	"Option4" : "Scraps from the hyena's carcass",
	"Question" : "What bait does Pi use to fish the first time?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0008",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02e538d248d1874fedb10"),
	"Ans" : "\"1\"",
	"Option1" : "He distracted him from the despair of being utterly alone and having lost his family",
	"Option2" : "He provided warmth",
	"Option3" : "He killed the dangerous hyena",
	"Option4" : "His weight kept the boat steadier",
	"Question" : "What was Pi grateful to Richard Parker for?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0009",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02f218d248d1874fedb11"),
	"Ans" : "\"1\"",
	"Option1" : "Kill the flying fish to use as bait",
	"Option2" : "Put the zebra out of its misery after the hyena tears its leg off",
	"Option3" : "Eat the zebra once it's been killed",
	"Option4" : "Kill the first dorado he catches",
	"Question" : "What does Pi have a hard time bringing himself to do?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0010",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
{
	"_id" : ObjectId("5ce02bd78d248d1874fedb0b"),
	"Ans" : "\"2\"",
	"Option1" : "The Tarpaulin",
	"Option2" : "Oars",
	"Option3" : "The zebra's bones",
	"Option4" : "Planks from the boat",
	"Question" : "What does Pi use as the base of his raft?",
	"QuestionID" : "Qs0004",
	"QuizID" : "Q0001"
},
